<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Getting Started on FedRAMP Automation</title><link>https://rene2mt.github.io/start/</link><description>Recent content in Getting Started on FedRAMP Automation</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><atom:link href="https://rene2mt.github.io/start/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Creating OSCAL-Based Content</title><link>https://rene2mt.github.io/start/creating/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://rene2mt.github.io/start/creating/</guid><description>The Guide to OSCAL-based FedRAMP Content provides important concepts necessary for working with any OSCAL-based FedRAMP file. Familiarization with those concepts is important to understanding this guide.
XML and JSON Formats The examples provided here are in XML; however, FedRAMP accepts XML or JSON formatted OSCAL-based SSP files. NIST offers a utility that provides lossless conversion of OSCAL-compliant files between XML and JSON in either direction.
You may submit your SSP to FedRAMP using either format.</description></item><item><title>Submitting OSCAL-Based Content</title><link>https://rene2mt.github.io/start/submitting/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://rene2mt.github.io/start/submitting/</guid><description>Submitting FedRAMP OSCAL-Based Content Coming Soon: Description of the submission process (what files to include, how to package, where submit, etc.)
P-ATO Submissions Coming Soon: Description of the submission process (what files to include, how to package, where submit, etc.)
Annual Authorizations Submissions Coming Soon: Description of the submission process (what files to include, how to package, where submit, etc.)
Continuous Monitoring Submissions Coming Soon: Description of the submission process (what files to include, how to package, where submit, etc.</description></item><item><title>Validating OSCAL-Based Content</title><link>https://rene2mt.github.io/start/validating/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://rene2mt.github.io/start/validating/</guid><description>Validating FedRAMP OSCAL-Based Content Coming Soon: Description of how to validate OSCAL content locally before submitting to FedRAMP. Will include links to tools and any instructions on how to validate locally.</description></item></channel></rss>